stopthethyroidmadness.com 2019-10-06

# Privacy Policy - Stop The Thyroid Madness

This privacy policy for _stopthethyroidmadness.com_ , also known as “this site” or “we” or “us”, describes how we use and protect any information that you give this site. We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. If you provide us with personal information, you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

## Website Visitors

Like most website operators, this site collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. The purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how this site’s visitors use this website. From time to time, this site may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate.

This site also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. We do not use IP addresses to identify visitors, and we do not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

## Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to this site choose to interact with this site in a way that requires the gathering of personally-identifying information. For example, if a visitor is making a comment on the blog post, it also includes the name they provide and the email.

In each case, this site collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with this site. We do not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

All of the information that is collected will be handled in accordance with GDPR legislation.

## Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

This site discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of project administrators, employees, contractors, or affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on the site or to provide services available through the site, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using this site, you consent to the transfer of such information to them.

The site will **not** rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than as described above, this site discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, if you give permission to have your information shared, or this site believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of this site, third parties, or the public at large.

If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of the contact form), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. This site takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration, or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

## Use of personal information

We will not sell or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.

## Legal grounds for processing personal information

We rely on one or more of the following processing conditions:

  * our legitimate interests in the effective delivery of information and services to you;
  * explicit consent that you have given;
  * legal obligations.

## Rights in relation to your information

You may have certain rights under data protection law in relation to the personal information we hold about you. In particular, you may have a right to:

  * request a copy of personal information we hold about you;
  * ask that we update the personal information we hold about you, or independently correct such personal information that you think is incorrect or incomplete;
  * ask that we delete personal information that we hold about you from live systems, or restrict the way in which we use such personal information (for information on deletion from archives, see the “Retention of personal information” section);
  * object to our processing of your personal information; and/or
  * withdraw your consent to our processing of your personal information (to the extent such processing is based on consent and consent is the only permissible basis for processing).

If you would like to exercise these rights or understand if these rights apply to you, please use the Contact form.

## Third Party Links

Our website may contain links to other websites provided by third parties not under our control. When following a link and providing information to a 3rd-party website, please be aware that we are not responsible for the data provided to that third party. This privacy policy only applies to the websites listed at the beginning of this document, so when you visit other websites, even when you click on a link posted on WordPress.org, you should read their own privacy policies.

### Cookies

Additionally, information about how you use our website is collected automatically using “cookies”. Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard internet log information and visitor behavior information. This information is used to track visitor use of the website and to compile statistical reports on website activity.

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, we may change this Privacy Policy from time to time, and at our sole discretion. We thus encourage visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

## Contact

Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy by using the Contact form.

_Important note: STTM is an information-only site based on what many patients worldwide have reported in their treatment and wisdom over the years. This is not to be taken as personal medical advice, nor to replace a relationship with your doctor. By reading this information-only website, you take full responsibility for what you choose to do with this website's information or outcomes. See theDisclaimer and Terms of Use._
